{
  "status": "success",
  "data": [
    {
      "username": "Kaushal_HwEU",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[1]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[1]",
      "calculated_score": 2860,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 3477,
      "calculated_points": 20,
      "question": "What is the name of the artificial intelligence framework developed by Facebook?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiVGVuc29yRmxvdyIsIjIiOiJUaGVhbm8iLCIzIjoiUHlUb3JjaCIsIjQiOiJDYWZmZSJ9",
      "options": {
        "1": "TensorFlow",
        "2": "Theano",
        "3": "PyTorch",
        "4": "Caffe"
      }
    },
    {
      "username": "Kaushal_HwEU",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[2]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[2]",
      "calculated_score": 2820,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 5673,
      "calculated_points": 20,
      "question": "Which technology uses neural networks to enable machines to understand and generate human language?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiUm9ib3RpY3MiLCIyIjoiTmF0dXJhbCBMYW5ndWFnZSBQcm9jZXNzaW5nKE5MUCkiLCIzIjoiQmxvY2tjaGFpbiIsIjQiOiJDb21wdXRlciB2aXNpb24ifQ==",
      "options": {
        "1": "Robotics",
        "2": "Natural Language Processing(NLP)",
        "3": "Blockchain",
        "4": "Computer vision"
      }
    },
    {
      "username": "Kaushal_HwEU",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[1]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[1,2]",
      "calculated_score": 0,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 1521,
      "calculated_points": 10,
      "question": "Which of the following landmarks are located in Paris?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiRWlmZmVsIHRvd2VyIiwiMiI6IkJpZyBCZW4iLCIzIjoiTm90cmUtZGFtZS1jYXRoZWRyYWwiLCI0IjoiQ29sbG9zc2V1bSJ9",
      "options": {
        "1": "Eiffel tower",
        "2": "Big Ben",
        "3": "Notre-dame-cathedral",
        "4": "Collosseum"
      }
    },
    {
      "username": "Kaushal_HwEU",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[1]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[1,3]",
      "calculated_score": 0,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 1309,
      "calculated_points": 20,
      "question": "Which cities are known for their iconic carnival celebrations?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiUmlvIGRlIEphbmVpcm8iLCIyIjoiSXRhbHkiLCIzIjoiVVNBIiwiNCI6IlVLIn0=",
      "options": {
        "1": "Rio de Janeiro",
        "2": "Italy",
        "3": "USA",
        "4": "UK"
      }
    },
    {
      "username": "Kaushal_HwEU",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[1]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[1]",
      "calculated_score": 2333,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 4863,
      "calculated_points": 15,
      "question": "What is the name of the open-source platform for building and training machine learning models developed by Google?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiVGVuc29yRmxvdyIsIjIiOiJTY2lLaXQiLCIzIjoiUHl0b3JjaCIsIjQiOiJLZXJhcyJ9",
      "options": {
        "1": "TensorFlow",
        "2": "SciKit",
        "3": "Pytorch",
        "4": "Keras"
      }
    },
    {
      "username": "Ridham_q5R5",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[2]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[1]",
      "calculated_score": 0,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 5783,
      "calculated_points": 0,
      "question": "What is the name of the artificial intelligence framework developed by Facebook?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiVGVuc29yRmxvdyIsIjIiOiJUaGVhbm8iLCIzIjoiUHlUb3JjaCIsIjQiOiJDYWZmZSJ9",
      "options": {
        "1": "TensorFlow",
        "2": "Theano",
        "3": "PyTorch",
        "4": "Caffe"
      }
    },
    {
      "username": "Ridham_q5R5",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[3]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[2]",
      "calculated_score": 0,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 3931,
      "calculated_points": 0,
      "question": "Which technology uses neural networks to enable machines to understand and generate human language?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiUm9ib3RpY3MiLCIyIjoiTmF0dXJhbCBMYW5ndWFnZSBQcm9jZXNzaW5nKE5MUCkiLCIzIjoiQmxvY2tjaGFpbiIsIjQiOiJDb21wdXRlciB2aXNpb24ifQ==",
      "options": {
        "1": "Robotics",
        "2": "Natural Language Processing(NLP)",
        "3": "Blockchain",
        "4": "Computer vision"
      }
    },
    {
      "username": "Ridham_q5R5",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[1]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[1,2]",
      "calculated_score": 0,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 3184,
      "calculated_points": 10,
      "question": "Which of the following landmarks are located in Paris?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiRWlmZmVsIHRvd2VyIiwiMiI6IkJpZyBCZW4iLCIzIjoiTm90cmUtZGFtZS1jYXRoZWRyYWwiLCI0IjoiQ29sbG9zc2V1bSJ9",
      "options": {
        "1": "Eiffel tower",
        "2": "Big Ben",
        "3": "Notre-dame-cathedral",
        "4": "Collosseum"
      }
    },
    {
      "username": "Ridham_q5R5",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[3]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[1,3]",
      "calculated_score": 0,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 3368,
      "calculated_points": 20,
      "question": "Which cities are known for their iconic carnival celebrations?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiUmlvIGRlIEphbmVpcm8iLCIyIjoiSXRhbHkiLCIzIjoiVVNBIiwiNCI6IlVLIn0=",
      "options": {
        "1": "Rio de Janeiro",
        "2": "Italy",
        "3": "USA",
        "4": "UK"
      }
    },
    {
      "username": "Ridham_q5R5",
      "selected_answer": {
        "String": "[1]",
        "Valid": true
      },
      "correct_answer": "[1]",
      "calculated_score": 2387,
      "is_attend": true,
      "response_time": 1169,
      "calculated_points": 15,
      "question": "What is the name of the open-source platform for building and training machine learning models developed by Google?",
      "raw_options": "eyIxIjoiVGVuc29yRmxvdyIsIjIiOiJTY2lLaXQiLCIzIjoiUHl0b3JjaCIsIjQiOiJLZXJhcyJ9",
      "options": {
        "1": "TensorFlow",
        "2": "SciKit",
        "3": "Pytorch",
        "4": "Keras"
      }
    }
  ]
};